<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dolphin NIE</title>
    <link>https://NYH-Dolphin.github.io/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Dolphin NIE</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://NYH-Dolphin.github.io/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Nested Wave Function Collapse Enables Large-Scale Content Generation</title>
      <link>https://NYH-Dolphin.github.io/en/research/n_wfc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://NYH-Dolphin.github.io/en/research/n_wfc/</guid>
      <description>This research was first accepted by IEEE Conference on Games 2023 and was extended to journal paper for IEEE Transactions on Games 2024. We won the Best Paper Award🏆 for IEEE Conference on Games! Congratulations to all the authors and their contributions to this paper! Thanks to NYU Tandon Game Innovation Lab for supporting the publication of this paper!
 1. What is Wave Function Collapse (WFC)? Wave Function Collapse (WFC) algorithm has been introduced by Maxim Gumin for Texture Synthesis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Point(s) of View(ing)</title>
      <link>https://NYH-Dolphin.github.io/en/project/pov/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://NYH-Dolphin.github.io/en/project/pov/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo 01 How to modify my website</title>
      <link>https://NYH-Dolphin.github.io/en/study/hugo01-how-to-modify-my-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://NYH-Dolphin.github.io/en/study/hugo01-how-to-modify-my-website/</guid>
      <description>1. Gokarna Template Introduction My website is based on a beautiful and simple website framework: Gokarna. Developers are Yash Mehrotra and Avijit Gupta.
Gokarna focuses on ultimate minimalism and simplicity. 😊
Basic Guide  Gokarna Website Template: https://gokarna-hugo.netlify.app/ Theme Documentation - Basics Theme Documentation - Advanced  Contribution I really love the design style of this website. Thus I will continue reporting issues and providing suggestions. Gokarna&amp;rsquo;s developers are keen on revising, and they accept pull requests (Though is not that fast, they keep doing it 💕).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>